<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Nesting India</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Nesting India</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">service@nestingindia.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="rupees">\u20B9</string>

    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="CodeColor">"#7C7B7B"</string>
    <string name="red">"#FA064B"</string>
    <string name="green">"#2B9E31"</string>
    <string name="yellow">"#FD9D02"</string>


    <string name="google_maps_key">AIzaSyB1IsqsIRUjQ8bKqdfju-RRk7ag3Re_2R8</string>

    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="action_geolocate">Pick Place</string>
    <string name="default_info_title">Default Location</string>
    <string name="default_info_snippet">No places found, because location permission is disabled.</string>


    <string name="select_address">Select Address</string>
    <string name="no_address">Not a valid Address</string>
    <string name="search_address">Search Address</string>
    <string name="confirm_address">Confirm Address</string>


    <!--    <string name="privaypolicy1">"This Privacy policy is subject to the terms of the Site Policy (User agreement) of Nesting India. This policy is effective from the date and time a user registers with Nesting India by filling up the Registration form and accepting the terms and conditions laid out in the Site Policy."</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="privaypolicy2">"In order to provide a personalised browsing experience, Nesting India may collect personal information from you. Additionally some of our websites may require you to complete a registration form or seek some information from you. When you let us have your preferences, we will be able to deliver or allow you to access the most relevant information that meets your end."</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="privaypolicy3">"To extend this personalized experience Nesting India may track the IP address of a user's computer and save certain information on your system in the form of cookies. A user has the option of accepting or declining the cookies of this website by changing the settings of your browser."</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="privaypolicy4">"The personal information provided by the users to Nesting India will not be provided to third parties without previous consent of the user concerned. Information of a general nature may however be revealed to external parties"</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="privaypolicy5">"Every effort will be made to keep the information provided by users in a safe manner, the information will be displayed on the website will be done so only after obtaining consent from the users. Any user browsing the site generally is not required to disclose his identity or provide any information about him/her, it is only at the time of registration you will be required to furnish the details in the registration form."</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="privaypolicy6">"A full user always has the option of not providing the information which is not mandatory. You aresolely responsible for maintaining confidentiality of the User password and user identification and all activities and transmission performed by the User through his user identification and shall be solely responsible for carrying out any online or off-line transaction involving credit cards / debit cards or such other forms of instruments or documents for making such transactions and IEIL assumes no responsibility or liability for their improper use of information relating to such usage of credit cards / debit cards used by the subscriber online / off-line."</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="privaypolicy7">"You agree that IEIL may use personal information about you to improve its marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve the Site's content and product offerings, and customise the Site's content, layout, and services. These uses improve the Site and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customised experience while using the Site."</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="privaypolicy8">"You agree that IEIL may use your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Site. By accepting the User Agreement and Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information. If you do not wish to receive these communications, we encourage you to opt out of the receipt of certain communications in your profile. You may make changes to your profile at any time. It is the belief of IEIL that privacy of a person can be best guaranteed by working in conjunction with the Law enforcement authorities."</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="privaypolicy9">"All IEIL websites including Nesting India fully comply with all Indian Laws applicable. IEIL has always cooperated with all law enforcement inquires. IEIL may disclose all or part of your personal details in response to a request from the law enforcement authorities or in a case of bonafide requirement to prevent an imminent breach of the law"</string>-->


    <string name="terms">"This website, www.nestingindia.com, (hereinafter referred to as Nesting India) is owned, hosted and operated by Nesting India, a company incorporated in India under the Companies Act, 1956 and having its registered office Nesting India. These terms and conditions regulating use of these Services constitute a legally binding agreement between Nesting India and the User (the “Agreement”).\n\nNesting India and/or any other website(s) linked to this website is an online information and communications service provided to you, subject to your compliance with the terms and conditions set forth below.\n\nPLEASE READ THIS DOCUMENT CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING OR USING Nesting India, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH BELOW. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ANY OF THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS, YOU SHOULD NOT ACCESS OR USE Nesting India. IF YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS ABOUT THESE TERMS, PLEASE CONTACT ( legal@Nesting India.com )\n\nNesting India may amend/modify these terms and conditions at any time, and such modifications shall be effective immediately upon posting of the modified terms and conditions on Nesting India. You may review the modified terms and conditions periodically to be aware of such modifications and your continued access or use of Nesting India, shall be deemed conclusive proof of your acceptance of these terms and conditions, as amended/modified from time to time Nesting India may also suspend the operation of Nesting India for support or technical upgradation, maintenance work, in order to update the content or for any other reason.\n\nIf you utilize Nesting India in a manner inconsistent with these terms and conditions, Nesting India may terminate your access, block your future access and/or seek such additional relief as the circumstances of your misuse may be deemed to be fit and proper.\n\n<b>DEFINITIONS</b> \nThe term Subscriber would include any person, whether an individual or a legal entity who has subscribed to the Services of Nesting India (whether on a paid or free basis), and to whom the access to Nesting India is restricted by the use of a sign in user name and a password. The user name and password are either allotted by Nesting India or chosen by the Subscriber or agreed upon by Nesting India. It is made abundantly clear that only the authorised User has the right to access the Services so offered by Nesting India.\nThe term Browser/Visitor will mean and include a person who utilizes any of the Services offered by Nesting India, without the need or a requirement to create an account i.e. visits non-restricted portions of Nesting India.\nThe use and access to Nesting India shall be subject to these terms and conditions. For the purposes of this Agreement, any person who does not have a legal or a contractual right to access the Services, but does so, will fall within the definition of an unauthorised user and will nevertheless be subject to the terms and conditions regulating the usage of Nesting India, and expressly so with respect to respecting the intellectual property rights of Nesting India, and abiding by terms and conditions below mentioned.\nThe terms User and Customer would include both the Subscriber/Advertiser(s) and Browser/Visitor(s)\nThe terms Service or Services would mean to include the interactive online information service offered by Nesting India on the internet through which the user may access information carried by Nesting India in the database maintained by it. The terms would also include to mean the search tools through which the User can search through the hosted databases and information using a number of search tools that are present with a selection matching their search criteria. The term would also include services by way of space used by customers for advertisements such as listings and banners. Users then select one or more of the items presented to view the full document/ record. The term Service does not extend to Nesting India acting as an agent either express or implied on behalf of any User/Customer and is merely acting as a medium of information exchange.
The term RERDA shall mean and include the Real Estate (Regulation and Development) Act, 2016 (http://mhupa.gov.in/User_Panel/UserView.aspx?TypeID=1535) as amended read with any rules or regulations that might be framed thereunder.\nThe term LMA shall mean and include the Legal Metrology Act, 2009 (https://consumeraffairs.nic.in/acts-and-rules/legal-metrology/the-legal-metrology-act-2009) as amended read with any rules or regulations that might be framed thereunder.\n\n<b>SUBMISSION AND ADMINISTRATION OF LISTINGS/ADVERTISEMENTS</b> \nAny User agrees not to submit any property descriptions, photographs, financial, contact or other information contained in each propertys data to Nesting India unless the User submitting such a Listing/Advertisement has acquired received all necessary rights and authorizations from the owner of such property or the power-of-attorney holder, including from the photographer and/or copyright owner of any photographs, to publish and advertise the said Property(s) on the Users website or on Nesting India. Similarly, Nesting India doesn’t take any ownership, directly or indirectly towards any person whatsoever, with respect to banners hosted on its website by its customers, which are strictly in the nature of sale of space by Nesting India and it has not carried out any independent verification on the authenticity or compliance requirements, as may have been required under any law for the time being in force, of such images/ banners/ listings. In case a User is covered under the RERDA, it shall have to ensure adherence of all compliance necessary, including but not limited to obtaining the necessary registrations etc. The User shall disclose all material information as required by LMA and in respect of their registrations under RERDA and all such property(s) submitted including the present status and nature of such property and shall also disclose whether the property is free from all encumbrances or not. The User in addition shall furnish a brief background of such property in respect of title, ownership and possession, Nesting India may also require the User to support his/her claims with respect to the status of the property with such documents as may be specified by it from time to time. The User may further be required to substantiate his claims as to the nature and status of the property by swearing an affidavit stating the authenticity of the information/data so provided/displayed. Nesting India may, at its sole discretion but without any obligation to, search for such and remove properties that are alleged to have been submitted in violation of this provision. In addition, Nesting India may require additional evidence of compliance with this provision from Users who are alleged to have submitted properties or other information/data in violation of these terms and conditions Nesting India will, in its sole discretion, terminate the accounts of, and refuse Service to, any User who repeatedly or intentionally violates these terms and conditions . Additionally, the User agrees to allow the Property listing, or any part of it, to be searched, displayed, accessed, downloaded, copied, and otherwise referred to by users of the Users website or the Nesting India website Nesting India shall have the sole authority to choose the manner in which any Property will be searched, displayed, accessed, downloaded, copied, and otherwise used on Nesting India Nesting India shall have the right to modify the property listing in the exercise of its rights under these terms and conditions. In addition to the terms aforementioned the User agrees\n(a) to represent and warrant that all Properties and associated information provided by the User will be accurate;\n(b) that the User will not permit the posting of a property on Nesting India under a name other than the name of a real estate agent who has been duly authorized and engaged by the owner of the property in this regard;\n\nNesting India shall place the information relating to properties at defined sections of Nesting India or such other mirror or parallel site Nesting India reserves, in a manner consistent with reasonable commercial business practices, the right to remove all or any part of the Properties posted on the Users website or on Nesting India without notice. Nesting India accepts no responsibility for checking/verifying the accuracy of reports or data files submitted by the User. While Nesting India shall take all reasonable efforts for data backup and business resumption, the User will be solely responsible for retaining back-up copies of all information, photographs and other materials furnished/submitted to Nesting India.\nUsers, who are buying/renting property/properties through Nesting India, must verify details the property/properties as well as its right, title, ownership, lien etc. on their own.\n\n<b>PAYMENT TERMS</b> \nPayments for the Services offered by Nesting India shall be on a 100% advance basis. The payment for Service once subscribed to by the subscriber is not refundable and any amount paid shall stand appropriated. Refund if any will be at the sole discretion Nesting India offers no guarantees whatsoever for the accuracy or timeliness of the refunds reaching the Users card/bank accounts. User acknowledges and agrees that Nesting India.com, at its sole discretion and without prejudice to other rights and remedies that it may have under the applicable laws, shall be entitled to set off the amount paid or payable by a subscriber/user against any amount(s) payable by User to Nesting India under any other agreement or commercial relationship towards other products/services. Nesting India gives no guarantees of server uptime or applications working properly. All is on a best effort basis and liability is limited to refund of amount only Nesting India undertakes no liability for free Services. Nesting India reserves its right to amend / alter or change all or any disclaimers or terms of agreements at any time without any prior notice. All terms / disclaimers whether specifically mentioned or not shall be deemed to be included if any reference is made to them.\n
Nesting India uses the maximum care as is possible to ensure that all or any data / information in respect of electronic transfer of money does not fall in the wrong hands. For completing online transactions involving payments a user is directed to a Payment Gateway Nesting India does not store or keep credit card data. Since the transaction happens on a third-party network not controlled by, once a credit card transaction has been completed, the payment information is not accessible to anyone at Nesting India after completion of the on-line transaction at the Payment Gateway, this ensures the maximum security Nesting India shall not be liable for any loss or damage sustained by reason of any disclosure (inadvertent or otherwise) of any information concerning the users account and / or information relating to or regarding online transactions using credit cards / debit cards and / or their verification process and particulars nor for any error, omission or inaccuracy with respect to any information so disclosed and used whether or not in pursuance of a legal process or otherwise.\n\nRefund in failed transactions
Though Nesting India payment reconciliation team works on a Nesting India basis, Nesting India offers no guarantees whatsoever for the accuracy or timeliness of the refunds reaching the Subscribers card/bank accounts. This is on account of the multiplicity of organizations involved in processing of online transactions, the problems with Internet infrastructure currently available and working days/holidays of financial institutions. Refunds in the event of wrong/objectionable property content being posted on the site would be at the discretion of Nesting India.\nIf you utilize Nesting India in a manner inconsistent with these terms and conditions, Nesting India may terminate your access, block your future access and/or seek such additional relief as the circumstances of your misuse may be deemed to be fit and proper.\n\n<b>USE OF INFORMATION</b> \nUser agrees to treat all information obtained from the Service, including listings, member directory, and any information otherwise made available to User in the Service (Content) as proprietary to Nesting India. User agrees that Content reserved for members will be maintained as confidential and shall be protected as a trade secret of Nesting India. Nesting India does not ensure the accuracy of, endorse or recommend any Content and a User uses such Content at the Users own risk. A User may access the listings/advertisements in the Service solely to obtain initial information from which further evaluation and investigation may commence. User shall limit access to and use of listings to personal and internal use, and shall not use listings obtained from the Service for further distribution, publication, public display, or preparation of derivative works or facilitate any of these activities in any way. User shall not use or reproduce any Content that is obtained from the Service, or that is otherwise made available to User in the Service, for or in connection with any other listing/advertising Service or device. User further shall not use the Service provided by the company in any other manner for or in connection with any other listing Service or device. Users violating these specific terms, specifically those Users searching the Service in an abusive or excessive manner, by automated or manual means, shall be subject to immediate termination of their membership without notice.\n\n<b>INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS</b> \nAll logos, brands, trade marks and Service marks (Marks) appearing in Nesting India are the properties either owned or used under license by Nesting India and / or its associates. All rights accruing from the same, statutory or otherwise, wholly vest with Nesting India / its associates. The access to Nesting India does not confer upon the User any license or right to use in respect of these Marks and therefore the use of these Marks in any form or manner, whatsoever is strictly prohibited. Any violation of the above would constitute an offence under the prevailing laws of India.\nNesting India respects the Intellectual Property Rights of all, it has and will continue to adhere to all the laws applicable in India in this respect Nesting India shall protect and respect the Intellectual Property Rights of the users as well as third parties to the best of its ability. In a case where a User(s) are found to be using Nesting India as a platform to infringe the Intellectual Property Rights of others Nesting India will be free to terminate this Agreement forthwith without any notice to the user.
By allowing Users to access Nesting India Nesting India grants the Users a limited, non-exclusive, non-assignable, revocable license (the License) to access and use the Services, provided that the User is in compliance with the terms and conditions of the Agreement.\n\n<b>RESTRICTIONS/ PROHIBITIONS</b> \nYou hereby expressly agree not to:
1.(a) Utilise the Services offered by Nesting India in any manner so as to impair the interests and functioning of Nesting India and which is non-compliant with laws and regulations including RERDA.\n2.(b) Access data not intended for you or log into server or account that you are not authorized to access;\n3.(c) Attempt to probe, scan or test the vulnerability of a system or network;\n4.(d) Attempt or breach security or authentication measures without proper authorization;\n5.(e) Attempt to interfere with, access to any other user including but not limited to by submitting a virus of any kind or Trojan horse to Nesting India, overloading, Flooding, mail bombing or crashing;\n6.(f) Copy, distribute, download, display, perform, reproduce, modify, edit, alter, enhance, broadcast or tamper with in any way or otherwise use any material contained in Nesting India except as permitted;\n7.(g) Copy and distribute this information on any other server, or modify or re-use information, text, graphics, sound, etc. on Nesting India to any other system. No reproduction of any part of Nesting India may be sold or distributed for commercial gain nor shall it be modified or incorporated in any other work, publication or Nesting India, whether in hard copy or electronic format, including postings to any other Nesting India;\n8.(h) Remove any copyright, trade mark or other intellectual property notices contained in the original material from any material copied or printed off from Nesting India or link to Nesting India, without our express written consent.\n9.(i) The user shall not utilise the Services offered by Nesting India in any manner so as to impair the interests and functioning Nesting India. The user undertakes not to duplicate, download publish, modify and distribute material on Nesting India.com unless specifically authorised by Nesting India in this regard. The user undertakes not to establish any deep link or other connection to any specific page of Nesting India other than the Home Page without obtaining prior consent of Nesting India, Nesting India strictly forbids copying, duplicating web pages or content using any automated process such as spiders, crawlers etc. or through any manual process for a purpose which has not been authorised in writing.\n10.(j) users undertake that the Services offered by Nesting India shall not be utilised to upload, post, email, transmit or otherwise make available either directly or indirectly, unsolicited bulk e-mail or unsolicited commercial e-mail. IEIL is not obligated to but reserves the right to filter and monitor and block the emails sent by you/user using the servers to maintained by Nesting India to relay emails. All attempts shall be made by Nesting India and the user to abide by International Best Practices in containing and eliminating Spam.\nThe User / subscriber / visitor to Nesting India or affiliated site(s) is prohibited from uploading, posting, transmitting, updating or sharing any information that:
belongs to another person and to which the user does not have any right to;
is grossly harmful, harassing, blasphemous, defamatory, obscene, pornographic, paedophilic, libellous, invasive of anothers privacy, hateful, or racially, ethnically objectionable, disparaging, relating or encouraging money laundering or gambling, or otherwise unlawful in any manner whatever;
harm minors in any way;
infringes any patent, trademark, copyright or other proprietary rights;
violates any law for the time being in force;
deceives or misleads the addressee about the origin of such messages or communicates any information which is grossly offensive or menacing in nature;
impersonate another person;
contains software viruses or any other computer code, files or programs designed to interrupt, destroy or limit the functionality of any computer resource;
threatens the unity, integrity, defence, security or sovereignty of India, friendly relations with foreign states, or public order or causes incitement to the commission of any cognisable offence or prevents investigation of any offence or is insulting any other nation.
Violations of system or network security may result in civil or criminal liability.\n\n<b>LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEB SITES</b> \nNesting India may provide links to other third-party World Wide Web sites or resources. Nesting India makes no representations whatsoever about any other Web site you may access through Nesting India.\n\n<b>DISCLAIMER AND WARRANTIES</b> \nNesting India is an intermediary as defined under sub-clause (w) of Section 2 of the Information Technology Act, 2000.
THE CONTENT OF Nesting India IS PROVIDED AS IS AND ON AN AS AVAILABLE BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR REPRESENTATIONS OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED.
NESTING INDIA AND ANY THIRD PARTY PROVIDING MATERIALS, SERVICES OR CONTENT TO THIS WEBSITE, DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, STATUTORY OR OTHERWISE INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, NON-INFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTY RIGHTS, COMPLETENESS OR ACCURACY OF THE INFORMATION, UPDATE OR CORRECTNESS OF THE INFORMATION, FREEDOM FROM COMPUTER VIRUSES, OTHER VIOLATION OF RIGHTS REGARDING SERVICES, PRODUCTS, MATERIAL AND CONTENTS OF Nesting India.
Views expressed by the Users are their own, Nesting India does not endorse the same and shall not be responsible for them. No claim as to the accuracy and correctness of the information on the site is made although every attempt is made to ensure that the content is not misleading/ offensive/ inappropriate. In case any inaccuracy is or otherwise improper content is sighted on the website, please report it to report abuse.
It is solely your responsibility to evaluate the accuracy, completeness and usefulness of all opinions, advice, Services, real estate and other related information listed on the website. Nesting India does not warrant that the access to website will be uninterrupted or error-free or that defects in website will be corrected.
Nesting India offers no guarantee no warrantees that there would be satisfactory response or any response at all, once the listing/banner is put on display. Any payments made to Nesting India /Nesting India are solely for the purposes of display of the property advertised.
Users are strongly advised to independently verify the authenticity of any Pre-Launch offers received by them. Nesting India does not endorse investment in any projects which have not received official sanction and have not been launched by the Builder/Promoter, users dealing in such projects shall be doing so entirely at their risk and responsibility.
No information contained herein shall constitute an invitation or an offer to invest in Nesting India or any of its Affiliates. Further, nothing contained in Nesting India should be construed as a recommendation to use any product, process, equipment or formulation, in conflict with any patent, or otherwise and Nesting India makes no representation or warranty, express or implied that, the use thereof will not infringe any patent, or otherwise.
Nesting India is controlled and operated from India and Nesting India makes no representation that the materials are appropriate or will be available for use in other parts of the World. If you use Nesting India from outside India, you are entirely responsible for compliance with all applicable local laws as well as international conventions and treaties.
Nesting India offers products, Services, content and various other functionalities through Nesting India and its affiliate sites to specific regions worldwide. The Services offered in one region may differ from those in other regions due to availability, local or regional laws or legal impediments and other considerations/factors. Nesting India does not make any warranty or representation that a User in one region may also obtain the Services as provided in another region. Information on Nesting India may contain references to products, programs or Services that are not announced or available in your country. Such references do not in any manner imply that Nesting India intends to announce, launch or provide such products, programs or Services in your country.\n\n<b>LIMITATION OF LIABILITY</b> \nNesting India will not be liable for any damages of any kind arising out of or relating to the use or the inability to use Nesting India, its content or links, including but not limited to damages caused by or related to errors, omissions, interruptions, defects, delay in operation or transmission, computer virus, line failure and all other direct, indirect, special, incidental, punitive, loss of profit, exemplary or consequential damages whether based on warranty, contract, tort or any other legal theory including Force Majeure, and whether or not, such organizations or entities were intimated or advised of the possibility of such damages.
Nesting India assumes no responsibility for any error, omission, interruption, deletion, defect, delay in operation or transmission, communication line failure, theft or destruction or unauthorised access to or alteration of Users data/information Nesting India shall not be responsible for any problem or technical malfunction on-line-systems, servers or providers, computer equipment, software, failure of e-mail or players on account of technical problem or traffic congestion on the Internet or at any website or combination thereof, including injury or damage to any User and/or Members or to any other persons computer related to or resulting from participating or downloading materials/information from the website.
Unless otherwise specified and notwithstanding anything contained in any other agreement or arrangement, by whatever name called, the performance obligation of Nesting India (service provider) is to provide access of its on-line portal to the customer for the duration of the subscription period and reference to any usage, by whatever name called or any other performance obligation, if any, is to provide the upper limit for consumption, which by itself, does not create any additional performance obligation upon Nesting India\n\n<b>TERMINATION</b> \nNesting India may, without notice in its sole discretion, and at any time, terminate or restrict your use or access to Nesting India (or any part thereof) for any reason, including, without limitation, that Nesting India based on its judgement and perception believes you have violated or acted inconsistently with the letter or spirit of these terms and conditions or any applicable law.\n\n<b>INDEMNIFICATION</b> \nSubmissions and unauthorized use of any information(s)/materials contained on Nesting India may violate copyright laws, trademark laws, the laws of privacy and publicity, certain communications statutes and regulations thereto and other applicable laws, statutes and its rules and regulations. You alone are responsible for your actions or the actions of any person using your user name and/or password.
You agree to defend, indemnify, and hold harmless, Nesting India and/ or its associates, subsidiaries, their officers, directors, employees, affiliates, licensees, business partners and agents, from and against any claims, actions or demands, including without limitation reasonable legal and accounting fees, alleging or resulting from your use of Nesting India material or your breach of these terms and conditions or any applicable law.
Nesting India will not be party to any legal proceedings between parties contracted through these Services. In case Nesting India is sought to implicated in any legal proceedings, costs will be recovered from the party that names Nesting India as a party to such proceedings. Nesting India shall abide with any court order served on it through due process.\n\n<b>PRIVACY POLICY</b> \nThe user of Nesting India is subject to Nesting India Privacy Policy (https://www.nestingindia.com/privacy) .\n\n<b>ARBITRATION</b> \nIf any dispute arises between a user/users and Nesting India arising out of use of the website or thereafter, in connection with the validity, interpretation, implementation or alleged breach of any provision of these terms and conditions, the dispute shall be referred to a sole Arbitrator who shall be an independent and neutral third party identified by Nesting India Decision of the Arbitrator shall be final and binding on both the parties to the dispute. The place of arbitration shall be nagpur. The Arbitration and Conciliation Act, 1996, shall govern the arbitration proceedings.\n\n<b>SEVERABILITY OF PROVISIONS</b> \nTHIS AGREEMENT between you and Nesting India governs your use of Nesting India. If any provision of these Nesting India terms and conditions or part thereof is inconsistent with or is held to be invalid/void by or under any law, rule, order or regulation of any Government or by the final adjudication of any court, such inconsistency or invalidity shall not affect the enforceability of any other provision of the terms and conditions.\n\n<b>WAIVER</b> \nThe failure of Nesting India to exercise or enforce any right or provision of the terms and conditions of use shall not constitute a waiver of its right to enforce such right or provision subsequently.\n\n<b>GOVERNING LAW</b> \nBy accessing Nesting India you agree that the laws prevailing in India shall be the governing laws in all matters relating to Nesting India as well as these terms and conditions.\n\n<b>JURISDICTION</b> \nCourts at Nagpur, India alone shall have the exclusive jurisdiction in all matters relating to Nesting India and these terms and conditions, irrespective of the territory and jurisdiction of your access to Nesting India.\nNesting India does not routinely monitor your postings to the web site but reserves the right to do so. However, if Nesting India becomes aware of an inappropriate use of Nesting India or any of its Services, Nesting India will respond in any way that, in its sole discretion, Nesting India deems appropriate. You acknowledge that Nesting India will have the right to report to law enforcement authorities any actions that may be considered illegal, as well as any information it receives of such illegal conduct. When requested, Nesting India will co-operate fully with law enforcement agencies in any investigation of alleged illegal activity on the Internet.
"</string>

    <string name="about"><b>Our story</b>\nA story have no beginning of end one choose the movement of experience from which To look back or from which To look ahead it a journey you have to travel by Winning all the hurdle That come through your path of success never stop just move forward And delivered the best you can.\n\n<b>About company</b>\nClient first is our moto company  working or communication commitment and are the basic values of our company and build a long term relationship throughout every activity that we undertake by listing and talking the taking to understand our clients needs we measure our success by the result delivered to client our ethics are build on commitment to offer superior costomer service.\n\n<b>Our Vission</b>\nOur vision is to be the leading real estate services provider in the region we aim to be the forefront of property marketing and to provide innovative solution that fit our client individuals property and situation to ensure the best possible out come. Is achieve to make the buying and selling of real state as cost effective as possible while maintaining the highest level of service .the best intrust of our client will always come first and we will place the clients concern ahead of our own  in each and every from as we are dedicated to development of long term client relationship."</string>
    <string name="sliver1">Extra Visibility\nPreferential Visibility in search result\nVerified Tag post verification\nProfessional Assistance\n\n<b>Other benefits</b>\nPhotos upload\nUnlimited posting properties posting\nPin your location in google for\nLocation,link number sharing\nShortlisted properties\n→Mail→ 500\n<b>Dealer/ Broker, Builder,  Owner.</b></string>

    <string name="gold1">Extra Visibility \nPreferential Visibility in search result \nVerified Tag post verification \nSpecial e-mail promotional alerts \n<b>Other Benefits</b> \nBanner \ntag \nunlimited posting \nproperty photos \nMobile Assistance/guidance \npin your location in google for free \nlocation, link and number \nshort-listed property \n1000 Mail \n1000 sms \n <b>Dealer / broker / builder.</b></string>
    <string name="platinum1">Verified tag post verification \nPriority in search result \n<b>Other Benefits</b> \nlocation ,link and number sharing \nExtended duration on the site Post verification \nPhotos \nRecommended for sale type resale and rental \npin your location in google for free \nshortlisted properties \nbanner \ntag \nExtra visibility \nAdvertise \nTop 10 properties \nmobile Assistant \nProperty photos \nSocial media Fb ,Insta ,Twitter, Etc. \n1500 Mail \n1500 sms \n<b>Owner /dealer/builder.</b></string>
<!--    <string name="lbl_silver_data">Extra Visibility \n Preferential Visibility in search result \n Verified Tag post verification \n  <b>Other Benefits</b>\n Photos upload \n Unlimited posting properties posting \n Pin your location in google for \n Location,link & number sharing \n Shortlisted properties \n 500 Mail \n  <b>Dealer/ Broker , Builder, Owner</b></string>-->


</resources>
